<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ManGo</string>
    <string name="start" />
    <string name="close" />
    <string name="time_bomb_message">
        秦香蓮三十二歲 那狀告當朝駙馬郎 欺君王瞞皇上 悔婚男兒招東床 秦香蓮三十二歲 那狀告當朝駙馬郎 欺君王瞞皇上 悔婚男兒招東床
    成为第一个知道[ManGo]的折扣和优惠的人！前往链接加入我们的 VIP 名单：[https://github.com/henly09/PlantApp_CAP102]。</string>
    <string name="write_message">Write Message</string>
    <string name="no_data_avail">Hey! Make your profile a little non empty.</string>
    <string name="title_intro">Mango Planting Manual</string>
    <string name="Retrieving_Data_Error">Data Error, Try Refreshing.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="intro">In an agricultural system, trees provide a variety of purposes in general.
        Through the production of fruits, vegetables, starch, and fodder, trees directly support the
        nutritional needs of families, communities, and livestock. In terms of the environment, trees
        help improve the soils and microclimates in the area, which increases food production and is
        especially beneficial for ecosystems that are fragile. In addition to supplying readily available
        building materials, trees are a significant source of fuel wood for farmers and rural communities
        as it is sometimes the sole source of energy in these places.Fruit trees, however, are more directly useful to humans in terms of nutrition and food because
        they produce fruits that are high in vitamins, proteins, vital fatty acids, and energy. As a result,
        fruit trees, both in rural and urban areas, play a significant part in the nutrition of children,
        women, and men. For instance, mango fruit is a great source of vitamins A, C, and B6, which are
        essential elements that primarily support healthy vision and a robust immune system for bodies that
        work normally.Farmers do not have a lot of experience with fruit trees, especially when it comes to planting them.
        Most of these farmers lack the fundamental knowledge necessary to establish fruit trees, such as
        timing considerations, technical details, and maintenance strategies. Its crucial to remember that
        planting fruit trees involves planning and preparation in order to ensure their health and productivity.
    </string>

    <string name="title_seed">Planting Mango Seedling</string>

    <string name="seed">African nations widely cultivate mango trees (Mangifera indica L.). Mangoes are both a
        revenue crop and a food source for farmer families. For its sweet and aromatic fruits, which may be
        consumed fresh or made into juice, jam, fruit leather, chutney, or dried fruits, Kenyans grow both
        indigenous and alien species that have been naturalized there. The demand for high-quality mango fruits
        for both domestic and international markets has significantly expanded in mango-producing regions.
    </string>

    <string name="title_step">Things to think about before planting a grafted mango seedling;</string>
    <string name="step">that there is sufficient land available for planting the seedling, ideally away
        from buildings and other structures or installations like telephone or power poles, water pipelines, or
        power lines,
        . that the topography, fertility, and soil characteristics of the chosen place are suitable for planting
        the mango type, and
        . the planted mango sapling has access to enough sunshine.</string>

    <string name="title_step1">Step1: Assemble all necessary components.</string>
    <string name="step1">Gather all the tools and supplies required, including the grafted mango seedlings,
        manure and/or fertilizer, a watering container, a shovel, and a hoe (jembe).</string>

    <string name="title_step2">Step2: Choosing which seedlings to place</string>
    <string name="step2">A healthy seedling that is large enough to plant should be sought out since they
        have a better chance of surviving. For an excellent production/high yields, quality planting material
        (grafted) is essential. Seedlings should be chosen if they dont exhibit illness or pest symptoms.</string>

    <string name="title_step3">Step3: Seedlings are transported for planting.</string>
    <string name="step3">Depending on how far it is from the nursery to the designated planting location,
        several methods of conveyance are employed for seedlings. Take care while transporting seedlings to
        avoid stacking them on top of one another, since this might harm the young trees. As this will lessen
        the possibility of harming them, it is advised that the seedlings be transported upright in boxes, plastic
        crates, or bags.
        Before moving them from the nursery to the planting location, water the seedlings youve chosen. To prevent
        the seedling from drying out while being transported, watering is done.</string>

    <string name="title_step4">Step4: Preparing the ground and planting</string>
    <string name="step4">Mango trees grow best in humid tropical and semi-arid subtropical climates, as long
        as there is a dry interval of at least three to four months and there is enough light to trigger blooming.

        Mango tree spacing varies depending on the kind and growth conditions (dry and wet zone). The optimum
        spacing is 12 m × 12 m in moist and rich soils due to extensive vegetative development, however in the
        dry zone the spacing varies from 10 m x 10 m due to the restricted vegetative growth.

        Wherever feasible, planting holes should be created prior to the start of a rainy season so that water
        can accumulate there to improve the survival of the seedling that is planted. The holes should be
        excavated to a depth of one meter, one meter in breadth, and one meter in length (1m x 1m x 1m).

        These holes should be spaced taking into account both the soil fertility and the mango tree canopy.</string>

    <string name="title_step5">Step5: Planting the seedling</string>
    <string name="step5_1">When planting is ready, re-fill the planting holes with a quarter of the topsoil
        from the area surrounding the hole or the soils that were eliminated during hole preparation (s).
        If required, properly combine this soil with the specified amounts of tree fertilizers or farm yard
        manure at a ratio of 3:1, as appropriate.</string>
    <string name="step5_2">While holding the seedling upright, cut the plastic bag or tube off on the side or bottom.
        The seedling should be somewhat banged from the top if it was nurtured in a tin or other container, though.
        After that, holding the seedling at the stems base, remove it from the tube or container containing the soil.
        While doing this, take care to avoid disturbing the root systems.</string>
    <string name="step5_3">Put the seedling into the hole. Topsoil should be added to the hole halfway, and
        it should be carefully pressed toward the root. Before entirely burying the hole in dirt, overflow the
        hole with water and let it drain. Make cautious to accomplish this without disturbing the dirt surrounding
        the roots or damaging them by bending them.</string>
    <string name="step5_4">By gently pushing down the earth surrounding the seedling, you may create a basin around
        the trees base.After watering, the basin will aid in holding the water. Make sure the seedling is positioned upright,
        just how it was on the polythene tube at the nursery.
        Under young trees, spread a layer of mulch. Mulch prevents moisture loss and weed competition while providing
        organic matter, a key source of tree nutrients and food for beneficial soil microorganisms.</string>

    <string name="title_manage">Management of fruit tree after planting</string>
    <string name="irrigation">Irrigation:</string>
    <string name="irrigation1">To encourage healthy establishment, water should be applied as soon as a plant is
        planted in the ground.
        If you want to increase your mango trees yields, water it every 8 to 12 days from the time the fruit
        begins to blossom until it reaches maturity.
        Two to three months before to flowering, watering is not advised as it will promote greater branching
        and leaf growth.:</string>

    <string name="protection">Protection:</string>
    <string name="protection1">It is necessary to construct a fence made of sticks or net around the fruit
        tree in order to protect it from livestock, particularly goats, when the fruit tree is placed in an
        open field, especially in cases when animals are also grazing there.</string>

    <string name="manure">Application of fertilizer and manure:</string>
    <string name="manure1">Start putting nitrogenous fertilizers on the ground after around 3 to 6 months
        (in the case of fruit trees e.g. mango, pawpaw, oranges). In order to prevent leaching out, use
        nitrogenous fertilizers at intervals (downward movement of useful minerals or nutrients in water).
        Fertilizers can also be replaced by mulching, correctly prepared compost or manure from the farmyard,
        and ash from the kitchen (leftover from cooking).</string>

    <string name="pruning">Pruning and training:</string>
    <string name="pruning1">Controlling the fruit trees height and shape is necessary.
        With this, the tree will be guided and made easier to harvest in its latter phases. In order to form
        the tree into the desired shape, trimming should be done in the first year. Seedling trees also encourage
        side branches when they are approximately 1 m from the ground. After the fruit has been harvested, prune
        the tree later for optimum tree upkeep. All branches at knee level (about 0.5 m) should be clipped, and
        height should be kept to no more than around 3.5 m. Get rid of all the dead branches so that sunlight can
        reach the ground beneath the tree from the canopy.</string>

    <string name="flowering">Fruit production and floral growth:</string>
    <string name="flowering1">Within two years of planting, fruit trees with grafts typically begin to bloom.
        At this point, fruit production should be discouraged since it may stunt the fruit trees development.
        It is recommended that fruit development be permitted for grafted mangoes starting in the fourth year.</string>

    <string name="pests">Illnesses and pests:</string>
    <string name="pests1">The most frequent pest for mangoes and other fruits is the fruit fly, which
        typically results in significant damage to and substantial losses of these crops. Among other
        techniques, the usage of fruit fly traps is a well-liked approach to managing fruit flies. Additionally,
        scale insects and gall midges are pests. The most prevalent mango diseases, powdery mildew and anthracnose,
        primarily attack the blooms and sensitive foliage and cause the formation of black blemishes on mango fruits.
        While anthracnose may be managed using copper fungicides, powdery mildew can be sprayed with Sulphur or
        Bayleton.</string>

    <string name="maturity">Development and harvesting:</string>
    <string name="maturity1">The maturity of the mangoes depends on the cultivar and might take anywhere from
        90 to 160 days after blossoming. Mangoes should not be plucked from the tree by being bashed with a stick
        and falling to the ground. Proper harvesting techniques are required. Hand picking is recommended, and
        if at all feasible, the fruit should still have a 2- to 3-cm stem attached. This lessens the latex that,
        if the fruit is picked improperly, may coat it. Fruits are often selected as their exterior color starts
        to change, for example, in certain cultivars, from deep green to light green. Fruit should be hand-picked
        or clipped off using a long stock (the portion of the fruit that connects it to the branch), which should
        be approximately 2 to 3 cm long, and then it should be stacked in a box or container with the stalks facing
        down for market transportation. In order to prevent bruising, proper postharvest treatment calls for storing
        in boxes or crates rather than sacks.</string>

    <string name="bottom_sheet_option_view">View profile picture</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_option_select">Select profile picture</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_option_heading">Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_option_remove_photo">Remove Photo</string>

    <string name="bottom_sheet_background_option_select">Select background picture</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_background_option_view">View background picture</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_background_option_heading">Background Picture</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="alt_bottom_sheet_chevron">Bottom sheet expandable indicator</string>

    <string name="alt_bottom_sheet_max_results_button_minus">Decreasing maximum classified results
        button</string>
    <string name="alt_bottom_sheet_max_results_button_plus">Increasing maximum classified results
        button</string>
    <string name="alt_bottom_sheet_threshold_button_minus">Decreasing threshold of classified image
        results button</string>
    <string name="alt_bottom_sheet_threshold_button_plus">Increasing threshold of classified image
        results button</string>
    <string name="alt_bottom_sheet_thread_button_minus">Decrease the number of threads used</string>
    <string name="alt_bottom_sheet_thread_button_plus">Increase the number of threads used</string>

    <string name="label_interence_time">Inference Time</string>
    <string name="label_fps">Frames per Second</string>
    <string name="label_confidence_threshold">Threshold</string>
    <string name="label_max_results">Max Results</string>
    <string name="label_threads">Number of Threads</string>
    <string name="label_delegate">Delegate</string>
    <string name="label_models">ML Model</string>
    <string name="default_threshold">0.50</string>
    <string name="default_inference_time">0ms</string>
    <string name="default_max_results">1</string>

    <string-array name="delegate_spinner_titles">
        <item>CPU</item>
        <item>GPU</item>
        <item>NNAPI</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="models_spinner_titles">
        <item>MobileNet V1</item>
        <item>EfficientNet Lite0</item>
        <item>EfficientNet Lite1</item>
        <item>EfficientNet Lite2</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>